expandfurniture.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | Transform Your Space | Expand Furniture

**Security**

We implement a secure processing server on our site when collecting information to ensure a high level of security for your personal information entered such as bank details and credit card information.

**Personal Information**

When you interact with us, we automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”). This is statistical information used to monitor the usage of our website and for advertising purposes. This information does not include personal information.

**Cookies**

As you visit [expandfurniture.com](https://expandfurniture.com/), advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](https://app.adroll.com/account/signin), Google & Facebook, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with expandfurniture.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit the page [http](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[://](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[www](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[.](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[adroll](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[.](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[com](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[/](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[about](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[/](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)[privacy](https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising. Facebook Ad Policy: https://www.facebook.com/policies/ads/# . Google Ad Policy: https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en .
